increasefollowers.org 2013-09-05

# Get More Followers on Twitter Free - FollowMania / Privacy

**FollowMania Privacy Policy**   
This privacy policy describes the FollowMania’s regulations, policies and procedures regarding collection, use and disclosure of user information. FollowMania Service receives user’s information via the website, Services, software interface, as well as through third-party Services (the Service). By using any of the FollowMania Services, the user gives its consent to the collection, transmission, processing, storage, disclose and other use of information in accordance with this privacy policy. Regardless of country of residence of the host country or countries in which information is created, user’s information may be used by FollowMania in any country in which FollowMania operates. On the occasion of any questions or comments about this privacy policy, please contact privacy@FollowMania.com. 

**Gathering and using of information**   
Information given during registration. When registering FollowMania online Service user uses his Twitter account. Part of this data such as user name may be open to public view on its Services, including Follower lists. 

**Extra information**   
If someone sends us a message at one of the email address we can save the message, e-mail and contact information for answers. Additional information described in this section is given for user voluntary. 

**Log data**   
Our servers automatically record data (hereinafter Log data) they receive while user is using the Service. Log data can contain information such as user IP-address, browser type, domain, visit pages. This log may also include others processes such acts of ads or banner ads. 

**A cookie**   
Like many other Web resources FollowMania uses cookie technology to collect additional information using the website and to improve our Services. Cookie file - a small data file that is transmitted to the computer's hard drive. FollowMania may use a cookie as a session and persistent cookie files to better understanding of the principles and mechanisms for user interaction with our Services and tracking overall usage of our Services users and web traffic routing on its Services and to improve, upgrade and modernize the Service. Most web browsers automatically accept a cookie. You can change your browser settings so as to accept a cookie was prohibited or held on a user's query accept a cookie from Web sites that users visit. 

**Third-party Services**   
In order to provide Services and to better understand all aspects of using the FollowMania Services, uses various third-party solutions, for example Google Analytics. They can serve to collect information sent by browser as a computer's data on Web pages request. Such information could apply cookie files and IP-address of users. 

### Information sharing and disclosure 

**User Agreement**   
We may share your information which has been collected during the process by using our Services without the consent of the user. 

**Services**   
We use trusted third parties to perform certain functions and Services we provide. We can provide personal data to this third party, but only in scope required to implement its functions and Services and only with the duties of protection similar to this privacy policy. 

**Legislative requirements and injury**   
We may disclose user information if it considers necessary in accordance with law, regulations or rules of law, to ensure the safety of any person, to investigate fraud, issues of security or technical issues to protect the rights or property. 

**Reorganization of the company**   
In the case of FollowMania involvement in the process of bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets of information users can be sold or transferred as a result of such transaction. The promises concerning the protection of information described in this privacy policy remain such that can be applied to users' information, given that the new entity. Information that is personal or confidential. We may share or disclose information that is personal or confidential and also general non-personalized information such as information on the number of user’s followers. 

**Company policy concerning children**   
Our Service is intended for children under 13 years. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your permission, please Contact Us for privacy@FollowMania.com. We are not engaged in intentional collection of personal information about children under 13 years. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your permission we will take actions to remove such information and cessation of Services access to child. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**   
We reserve the right to periodically review this Privacy Policy. Current version, which regulates the use of information by user, you can always find at http://FollowMania.com/privacy.aspx. If in FollowMania’s opinion made the changes to the privacy policy are significant, we will notify users via e-mail message. By continuing to access or use Services after the changes effective date the user confirms agreement to implement revised privacy policy.
